Hi, everyone. Thanks for joining today. Can everyone see my screen and presentation.
Yes. Looks good. Yeah.
All right. And as a reminder, we're going to cover this right now, but this is not information that can be shared yet. And we'll talk about that at the end. So we'll take about five minutes here, just go through some of the updates so that you guys are aware time
And most of the changes that we're making around benefits are really in response to competition. So when we're talking to candidates and when they are sharing information about
What they're seeing from other companies or competitive offers that's that's really one of the main reasons that we are doing this.
So as an overview of what we do provide health vision and dental still providing that with PPO HMO options still providing life insurance and short and long term disability.
We still have our retirement options and then we're have our holidays and vacation with a couple changes that we'll get into in a minute.
If you need to refer back to this or want more information or the details later. Once those are published there'll be on. Mm hmm.
So get started on the package.
So let's see, we've got some updates in six different areas. The first is around healthcare.
So for employees. They can now have an HSA option and they are able to contribute 1500 dollars a year for their account and we will match that. It's simply a checkbox that the individual could do when they sign up and this account will be created automatically
Any questions on that.
Hey, Sam. It's Amanda Yeah quick question about the HSA account, there'll be a maximum contribution in addition to the 1500 we already put into the account.
Yeah, so we will be matching the employer contribution up to 1500 but the employee can contribute 4500
And
Their contributions will be made at the start, a year and spread out over their
their paychecks. So that will come out of their
Their pay and then that will get loaded onto a debit card that they can use for expenses.
Okay great, thanks.
So next one is insurance, we are making a small change extending around beneficiary support, you know, get more details on that but that helps us manage a little bit of the costs of providing life insurance to employees.
And the next one is around deferred comp. So we are going to add ability for anyone level eight and above to
Allow them to defer compensation for tax purposes or we're different years.
The same. It's Jeff soon the limit the amount of compensation, they can differ.
Yeah, so given that this is really to manage taxes, there is a limit of 120,000. So that's the amount that can be deferred. The rest will be taxed at the
Current here.
Any other questions on that.
Can we have a tax specialist available for them to speak to about the program.
Actually, that's a really good idea. Let me look to take some notes to
set that up.
Alright, the next three on this list of the biggest changes. The first is being able to offer a roth 401k. So in contrast to a traditional 401k Roth allows the employee.
To provide post tax money which is not them taxed at the time of retirement and then we are upping our contribution from 3% to 6% match that 6% match goes into a traditional 401k and will actually be that component will actually be taxed at retirement.
Then for vacation, we are switching from our current graduated schedule a time off to go to an unlimited schedule.
So this means as long as it is approved the employees in good standing. And there's minimal impact to projects are customers that employees can take as much time off as they need
A sandwich started. Is this similar to the vacation program that Twitter and others are offering it seems to be a popular recruitment item. Yeah.
That's one thing we're seeing is we're losing candidates who see this as a benefit when they get an offer to a competitor.
In practice, unlimited time off doesn't actually mean people are taking more than they would normally it just removes that perception of a ceiling.
On average, people are expected. So take about three weeks.
Then
The last change here which got approval from the board is to offer options and what are called restricted stock units are our skews
That will best over a three year timeframe and more information of that and the stock option program and how things are granted invest over time. What happens when Employees JOIN or leave is all posted on HR web
And there we go.
Any other questions before we wrap up.
Thanks. So these are great new benefits all the employees are really going to love them. Thank you.
Excellent. And there's more information on HR web and until then please kind of keep this between us and we'll have more communication tools for when ready.
Okay great, thanks.
Thank you.
Awesome work, Sam.
All right, thanks everyone.
See you later.